Hello friends, welcome to my channel 24. Today
I have brought a new job opportunity for you guys.
This positivity has come
from ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited. You must have
heard the name of ICICI Bank. It does insurance work under the
name of Lombard General Insurance Company Limited.
It is hiring for
remote job insurance advisor for its office in Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh.
Okay, this will be your part-time work
and it is freelance work, you can
work anytime as per your convenience. You can work
as much as you want.
Okay, as much as you want. Apart from this, if
you are a housewife, you can apply. If you are a
student, you can apply. If you are a businessman, you
can work in your free time. If you are a service man, if
you have more free time, you
can work in this. Extra income can be yours.
Okay, now let me tell you about it.
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Advisor location in Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh
is flexible area, which means as I
told you, it will be self-employed.  Determine
target and industrial leading PR
products to sell, okay, so it depends on you
how much work you
want to do, some people do
not like that people press them,
okay, so for them it
is very important and a
good opportunity for those who want to earn extra income
without any burden,
ICICI Lombard Advisor, you will have everything you need,
you will get good rewards here,
working in and
insurance company can help you advance
professionally, whether it is a temporary job and a
long term career, so if you
want to make it temporary, want to do a side business
or
you want to make a career in your pocket, okay,
it is good for both purposes, that is, if students
or housewives or businessmen
want to do it on the side, then it is also good, if
you want a career and you are
not able to understand in which field to move ahead, then
this is good for your career purpose also because
ahead in it, like right now you  If you
work as an insurance advisor or
you gain experience, then there are more
opportunities available in it. You
can also work as a manager in the office.
Okay, okay, for that reason,
you should join our team and
become an ICICI Lombard advisor.
He has written about himself that he pays a good
salary, he pays a good commission, he pays
so much commission that your
total income will be more than the salary.
He has written all this and join over the
team. Send your resume to
Nigam.
Okay, it is very easy. He has told you the date,
send it to his email ID.
And this is his WhatsApp number, this
is WhatsApp number
8655956223. Okay, so you can send your resume on this also and
talk to him.
Apart from this, he has also given his email ID,
you can apply directly on that, it is
very easy to apply, so I hope
you will like it very much because he is very
fortunate and nowadays there is a
lot of information about everything.